straponjane.com 2005-12-15

# Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment to Privacy  
**Your privacy is very important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and throughout this website, and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. **The Information We Collect:  
**This notice  applies to all information collected or submitted on this website  
 ([www.StraponJane.com](http://www.straponjane.com/)) On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include:  
**_Name:  
Email Address:  
Sex:  
Age:  
Country of Residence:  
Sexual Preference: _****The Way We Use Information:  
**The information we collect (Your name and email address) is used to provide  from time to time, special  offers and discounts for goods and services that we may provide. We DO NOT, sell, hire, lease or provide the information we collect about you to ANY other third party. The information we hold on you is strictly for our OWN use. **Our Commitment to Data Security  
**To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, administrative, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. **How you can Access or Correct Your Information  
**You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending an email addressed to [CustomerServices@StrapOnJane.com](mailto:CustomerServices@StrapOnJane.com) asking us to provide you with all information that we hold about you. You must provide a valid return email address for us to action your request. We will reply to you within 7 working days from receiving your email. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error in our records. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. **How to Contact Us  
**Should you have ANY other questions or concerns regarding these privacy policies, please send an email clearly detailing your inquiry or request to [webmaster@StraponJane.com](mailto:webmaster@StraponJane.com) **

Our Payment Processor’s Privacy Policy 

**[Click HERE for CCBILL Privacy Policy](http://www.ccbill.com/) concerning Collected Information **

Our Payment Processor’s Security Policy
